I left it behind on the plane.
[Sigh...]
Once it shows up on the lost and found list
[Clicking refresh like there's no tomorrow]
I keep refreshing the page.
I keep checking the flight info thoroughly.
I found it.
Next up.
Oh my.
Hello everyone, it's HYERI here.
Today, through Cosmopolitan's 'In My Box'
I'm going to introduce my cherished items.
I'm really going to show you some genuine treasures, so
Please look forward to it a lot.
[Drumroll]
First up!
Ta-da.
[Name: Today's Apple / Point: Lately, HYERI has been eating it every morning to start the day fresh]
I've been eating an apple every morning these days.
I mean, I've always liked apples, but
[Morning routine: Lounging around]
There are many times when I feel lazy in the morning, so
I just give it a quick wash.
Crunch!
I really feel like it helps me start the day fresh.
[Back to basics]
I've been good about eating apples again these days.
[Q. Do you meet 'Today's Apple' every morning?]
[A brief lapse in commitment]
Honestly, there are times I forget and don't eat it, but
As much as possible
I usually manage to eat it.
[Q. Does 'Today's Apple' feel neglected when you forget]
Ah...
Are you N?
Right, if it feels neglected
Just eat it!
[Crunch!]
[All good now]
Feeling neglected?
These days, I've been
Ta-da.
[Name: Uniqlo Ribbed Bra Top / Point: Perfect for the current season, comfortable and supportive]
This is a Uniqlo ribbed bra top.
Isn't it just so pretty, everyone?
How should I put it? It has great support.
It really holds you well.
And it's comfortable to move around in.
Really comfortable.
Really.
Even when you're moving a lot, it's comfortable.
I'm wearing the Uniqlo Bra Top right now too.
It's suitable enough to wear outside like this.
[Perfect for the current weather]
It's come out so beautifully.
Just throw on a shirt over it.
And head out.
It's the best!
Highly recommend!
Hmm! The next product is
The next product(?)?
Let's do it again.
[# Take 2]
Next, my
Cherished item.
Ta-da.
This little one.
[Name: Digital Camera / Point: A gift from my beloved sister Miyeon, it's been taking care of HYERI's Instagram feed lately]
It's a digital camera.
It's a digital camera gifted by my beloved sister Miyeon.
If you check out my Instagram feed
What's this? Why are there so many pretty photos?
More people must be noticing and commenting.
[The secret to the photos is the digital camera]
All the photos were diligently taken with this digital camera.
Thank you, Miyeon.
When Miyeon appeared on 'Hyel's club'
"Why do you take such pretty photos?"
I once asked like this
She seemed really interested in digital cameras.
So then
"Oh? Then I'll give you a gift, sis."
She mentioned it casually in passing.
[The gift was just perfect!]
Really, just like this
It fits me like a glove.
[Still deeply moved]
She gifted me a pink digital camera.
I'm using it very well.
[Good!]
[Joo I-jae]
Joo I-jae was my character name when I was filming the drama 'To You, Dream'.
The role name was Joo I-jae.
So, I have a sticker I got back then
[All matched up in pink]
I stuck it here because it's pink, too.
[Gathering things up]
Actually, this is quite unique
[Name: Toothbrush Sterilizer  Powder Toothpaste / Point: The sterilizer and surprisingly tingly powder toothpaste that HYERI uses daily these days]
These are my toothpaste and toothbrush.
It's toothpaste, but it's in powder form.
[Sterilization ON]
And this is something you can use for sterilization.
[Sterilization ON anytime, anywhere]
It's a portable sterilizer you can carry around.
This toothbrush is...
[Hesitant...]
Korean Air...
It's a toothbrush
You know how you brush your teeth on a plane?
It feels like such a waste to use it just once and throw it away.
[Disposable yet reusable]
So I use it a few more times.
Even if it's a disposable toothbrush
I carry it around and use it a few more times like this.
I carry the toothbrush in a sterilizer like this
Once you charge this
you can use it for quite a long time.
[One charge = several days of convenience]
I'm using it very conveniently.
I also received the toothpaste as a gift
[Have you heard of powder toothpaste?]
It's powder toothpaste like this.
You scoop it with a spoon like this
and then put it in your mouth before brushing.
[Unexpectedly strong freshness that lingers]
But it's surprisingly refreshing.
It's extremely refreshing.
[It's as intense as a spicy hotpot]
It's so refreshingly intense, it's almost numbing.
And then
Oh, this one
[Name: Bluetooth Keyboard / Point: An essential item for document work, protecting HYERI's eyes and thumbs]
Ta-da! This is my keyboard.
You just do it like this
[A keyboard to replace your thumbs]
It's a keyboard you can connect to your phone and use right away.
I've been doing a lot of document work on my phone lately, so
I carry it around with me
[Working hard, working hard]
I'm diligently working on documents.
Because my fingers hurt too much
Sometimes, it's really like
(Typing) hurts my eyes too much
My fingers hurt so much that I don't want to do it.
So I bought a keyboard.
I bought it myself.
Bought with my own money
[Bought with my own money]
I carry it around diligently
and I'm working on documents.
And I'm almost done, but
Ta-da.
[Name: Devialet Bluetooth Earphones / Point: The wired earphones HYERI used for 10 years are gone, and this is the new addition to the family]
These are Bluetooth earphones
For those who've watched my content a bit, you might know
I used wired earphones
[For a whopping 10 years]
I really used them for 10 years.
[Now they've gone far away...]
But they passed away
They've come to an end.
So I bought a new item.
It's a Devialet product
I already use Devialet speakers, so
Oh?
I was curious about how the earphones would be, so
I tried using them
and I'm very satisfied and using them well.
[Q. Don't you miss the wired earphones you used for 10 years?]
Yes! I do miss them.
It's kind of like...
They had this old-school vibe, you know
My earphones
They had their own charm.
There's something about them that you guys wouldn't understand.
[Suddenly remembered TMI]
TMI
Once, I was on a plane
And I left them behind
[Phew...]
I think it was around the AAA (Asia Artist Awards) time.
When the lost and found list was updated
[Clicking refresh until the F5 key wore out]
I kept refreshing and checking.
I searched flight info and kept checking.
I found them
I finally found them.
[Returned after going round and round]
They came back to my hands.
I won't lose them again.
They're expensive, you know.
This one, all at once.
Ta-da.
[Name: Moz Mint  Breath Care / Point: Mint pills and mint sticks, HYERI's must-haves for refreshing during seasonal changes]
Looking at it, I really like refreshing things.
[When it comes to breath care]
Usually, there are a lot of sprays
And a lot of chewables, right
But this one, you swallow it.
[Gasp]
I didn't know and kept chewing it.
After you swallow it
It feels really refreshing, like
You can do something refreshing.
[Refreshing(?)]
[Success]
Like this
I saw it from someone else's recommendation.
[Gasp]
"You mean you swallow that?"
Since then, I've been swallowing it.
I'm sure you all know this already, but
[Suddenly, an aroma therapy for nasal relief appears]
Mint aroma for your nose.
You know you're supposed to insert it up to here, right?
During the seasonal changes
I'm feeling a bit under the weather with a cold
Cold medicine makes you so drowsy.
I can't be sleepy while filming, so
I'm just getting by with these kinds of things.
Everyone, be careful not to catch a cold.
Wow, there's so much mint in my bag!
That was HYERI's 'What's in my box!'
[Good!]
I had such a beautiful photoshoot today.
I wore various bra tops with Uniqlo.
We took some really beautiful photos.
There were actual screams of excitement.
Please look forward to it a lot.
Please show lots of love for Cosmopolitan and me, HYERI.
Goodbye, everyone.
Stay happy.